Let me get this straight.
让我把事情搞清楚.
The company is selling vitamins.
这家公司在卖维生素.
Right.
对.
And vitamins come from a natural source.
而维生素是从天然物质中提取出来的.
No. Some vitamins do. These do not.
不. 有一些维生素是的, 而这些却不是.
But the label says they're natural.
但标签上说它们是纯天然的.
This sounds familiar.
这听起来挺耳熟.
Didn't we have a case like it a couple of years ago?
我们两年前不是有一个类似的案例吗?
The bottled water company.
那家瓶装水公司.
Yeah. They were bottling tap water and calling it mineral water.
对. 他们把自来水装入瓶中而把它称作矿泉水.
It's the same company.
是同一家公司.
What? We won that case.
什么? 我们打赢了那场官司.
They're in a new business. Vitamins.
他们做起了新生意. 维生素.
No, no, no. Let's pursue this one and put an end to it.
不行, 不行, 不行. 我们要追查下去, 并阻止他们.
Companies that do this should not be in business.
做这种事的公司就应该关门歇业.
OK. That's it. Time to go home.
好的. 就这样吧. 该回家了.
Joe, one more thing.
Joe, 还有一件事.
Yes?
什么?
Nancy and I have talked about it a lot and I am going to run for office.
我和Nancy就这件事谈了很多, 我打算竞选公职.
I won't announce it for a while,
我暂时还不会宣布,
but I wanted you to know.
但我希望你知道.
I appreciate that, Richard. Good luck.
谢谢, Richard. 祝你好运.
Don't forget to tell Marie.
别忘了告诉Marie.
Right.
好的.
Are you surprised?
你感到吃惊吗?
No. But it won't be easy Richard.
不吃惊. 但是这可不容易 Richard.
I always say that leaders are born but elected officials are very carefully manufactured.
我一直都说领袖是天生的, 而当选的官员都是精心包装出来的.
Hmm. I know.
Hmm. 我知道.
Let me know if there's anything I can do.
如果有要我帮忙的地方, 尽管开口.
Thanks, Joe. Manufactured, huh?
谢谢, Joe. 包装, huh?
Nothing personal.
不是针对你的.